# ALI HASSAN ALI

Alexandria, Agami | 01127344298 | alihgad2@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ali-hassan-gad/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/ali-hassan-gad/</a>

Portfolio: <a href="https://alihgad.github.io/portoflio/">https://alihgad.github.io/portoflio/</a>

GitHub: https://github.com/alihgad

#### **SUMMARY**

Front-end developer experienced in web developing technology such like Html, CSS, bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX and React.JS.

I applied what I learned in a practical way in several projects, developing a user-friendly web application, responsive cross all screens

#### **COURSES**

# Front-end diploma at route

Sep 2020 - Aug 2021

Offline attends with professional instructor, assignment every week for practical applying

**Studied Technologies**: HTML – CSS – Bootstrap –JavaScript

jQuery - AJAX - TypeScript - React JS and Next JS
(And needed libraries like: formik, react Query - axios)

yup - .....)

**Graduation project:** Fresh cart (E-commerce) (Handling front-end)

Link https://alihgad.github.io/commerce/

Repo: https://github.com/alihgad/commerce

Used Technologies: CSS - Bootstrap - JavaScript - React.js

# Back-end diploma at route

Apr 2024 – Till now

Offline attends with professional instructor, assignment every week for practical applying

Studding Technologies: Node js - Express js - Mongo DB - JOI

- REST Api - Socket.io - Graph QL - Docker - Nest JS

# **SKILLS**

Computer: Excel - Word - Power Point

Technical: HTML – CSS – Bootstrap – JavaScript – jQuery – Ajax – React – Next

Languages: Arabic mother tongue, good in English

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **American Eagle Outfitters**

sales | Alexandria Jun 2024 - Oct 2024

#### **Miniso**

- Team leader on more than 10 staff members - develop staff skills - time management Solve staff problems – arrange attendance schedule – solve customer problems presentation skills

Cashier | Cairo Sep 2020 – Aug 2021

Sales | Cairo Nov 2019 - Aug 2020

### **EDUCATION**

# Agricultural economy

Al-Azhar University | Faculty of agriculture | Cairo Aug 2022

# PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birth date: 7/5/1999 - Military service: Exemption